Today, we're going to talk about the one and only, Codex.
I'm sure you've all heard of this software by now.
This is OpenAI's flagship product.
It's a direct competitor to Anthropic's Claude Code.
Codex is capable of doing a whole lot of things.
It doesn't just help you write code,
debug issues,
run tests,
It can also manage Git and control your browser.
It can even directly control your computer to complete all sorts of tasks.
It's incredibly powerful.
But the more features there are, the harder it is to know where to start.
So in this video, I'm going to walk you through everything systematically.
the most essential features of Codex,
and help you build a solid framework for using it.
The entire video is divided into three parts.
The first part is the fundamentals.
and will mainly get you started with Codex quickly.
We'll also cover some key configurations and common pitfalls to watch out for.
Part two is the advanced section.
focusing on version control,
and session management,
and how to more effectively organize and progress your development tasks.
Part three is the Extensions section.
We'll explore how to use plugins and skills,
automation, and mobile, to further push the boundaries of what Codex can do.
to further push the boundaries of what Codex can do.
I've listed all the features and their corresponding timestamps.
I've listed them all in the table of contents.
Feel free to adjust it to your needs.
Alright, let's dive right in.
Let's get started.
Alright, the first thing we need to do is get Codex installed on our computer.
We can open this page.
Just go to https://chatgpt.com/zh-Hans-CN/codex/, click the download button right there, and you'll get Codex.
Once the download is complete,
Let's go ahead and open it.
The installation process is just like any other regular software.
For example, I'm on macOS.
Just drag the Codex icon into your Applications folder.
And just like that, the installation is complete.
Alright, now that it's installed,
Alright, let's open up Codex.
Once Codex is open,
The first thing it's going to do is prompt us to log in.
So, it gives us two options here.
The first one is to log in with your ChatGPT account.
This requires you to subscribe to a ChatGPT plan.
ChatGPT offers a variety of plans.
The most common ones are the ones I'm showing on my screen right now.
These are mainly the free version and the Plus plan.
the Plus and Pro plans.
So, as you can see on the screen, these are the different plans.
And the price goes up as you move from left to right.
And of course, the overall Codex credit you get also increases with each one.
So, as it stands,
The Codex quota for the Free and Go plans should be pretty much the same.
But once you get to the Plus plan, the allowance sees a significant jump.
And the Pro plan, naturally, gives you even more.
It's worth mentioning that
Even if you're on the free plan, the system still gives you a certain amount of Codex credit.
It's just that this allowance is incredibly small.
It's barely enough to get your feet wet.
So, if you really want to get the hang of it and see what it's truly capable of,
I'd recommend starting with the Plus plan.
It's twenty dollars a month.
The amount of available resources is pretty moderate.
Besides the subscription plans,
OpenAI also offers another option to use Codex.
And that is to use the API directly.
And that corresponds to this option right here: 'Sign in another way'.
After you click that, it'll prompt you to enter your OpenAI API key.
Generally speaking, using the API isn't as cost-effective as getting a subscription plan.
Plus, the barrier to entry for getting this API key is a bit high.
Usually, you'll need an international credit card for that.
So, I'd recommend just subscribing to a plan to use Codex.
Now, for the actual login process...
So I'm not going to show that part here.
From here, you can choose the login method that works best for you.
Alright, once you're logged in,
So, the first thing you'll see is an interface that looks something like this.
First, Codex will ask what we do for a living.
Just go ahead and choose the option that best fits your situation.
Then, Codex will prompt you to import settings from Claude Code and Cursor.
and import their related configurations into Codex.
We'll skip this for now.
Then Codex asks us if we want to try the mobile version.
We'll just click on 'Setup Later'.
I'll show you how this works in a bit.
So let's not worry about that for now.
Alright, so now we're officially in the Codex interface.
We're all set to start using it now.
Let's just say hi to it.
Let's see if it's working properly.
As you can see, Codex is up and running.
Alright, next I'm going to walk you through building a to-do list app.
And as we build this to-do app,
I'll walk you through all of Codex's different features.
First, we need to create a new directory.
to store our software code.
Let's open up Finder.
And create a new folder right here.
Let's call it 'Mark Notes'.
And now, let's head back to Codex.
Click on 'Work in the Project'.
Then, click on "Use an existing folder".
In the pop-up dialog box,
Select the folder we just created.
And then, click on 'Open'.
And you'll see that Codex has renamed the project directory to 'Mark Notes'.
This means that from now on, Codex
will place the code inside this folder.
Alright, with that, all the preparatory work is now complete.
Now, we can start making our requests.
So, for example, our requirement is to build a note-taking app using HTML.
The interface should be split into two sections, left and right.
The left side is the list of notes,
and the right side is for the note's content.
Finally, we'll remind it to make sure it runs proper tests.
Then, hit Enter to submit.
And that's when Codex will get to work.
And you can see it's just churning out code for us like crazy.
Of course, it's not actually this fast in a real-world scenario.
So, to save you all some time,
I've sped this part up.
The rest of the process, including the questions that follow,
have also been sped up to varying degrees.
Just so you know.
Alright, Codex has paused.
It suggests that it wants to build a local server.
Let's test out the HTML notes.
So, we have three options here.
The first option is 'Yes'.
This is pretty straightforward.
Basically, all you have to do is start up the local server, and you're good to go.
But in the future, if Codex makes a similar request,
we'll have to grant it permission again.
The second option means we're not just agreeing,
And for code like this that starts a local server, it can just run it directly from now on.
It won't need our authorization anymore.
The second option, you can think of it as 'disagree'.
It's not actually a button.
It's actually an input box.
Let's click on it and see.
Here, we can tell Codex how we want it to handle the task.
For instance, you could just have it check the code,
or start a local server, or anything like that.
Of course, if you don't agree with that,
And if you can't even be bothered to tell Codex why,
Or, you can just click the 'skip' button right here.
So this is basically Codex's toned-down version of a fourth option.
Alright, so we've covered all the available options.
So for this, we'll just go with the first option, 'Yes'.
And then, Codex asks for our permission to access it.
the newly created local server.
We'll agree to that as well.
And now, Codex has finished its job.
As you can see, the most important file in here...
is this one: index.html.
We can click to preview how it looks.
So, this is the note-taking app that Codex built.
It looks pretty standard.
You can find all the basic functions right here.
Of course, some of you might be thinking that this preview area is a bit too small.
and want to make it a bit bigger.
And of course, you can do that.
So let's go ahead and click this.
And just like that, the left panel is tucked away.
This gives us a lot more space for the preview.
But this bottom area here, it's also a bit of an eyesore.
So, can we hide it?
Actually, you can.
We can click on the three dots right here.
Then just select 'Hide Composer', and you're all set.
See? That's much better.
So, let's say at this point,
You're looking at these two notes on the interface, and you find them really distracting.
and you want to get rid of them.
And this is actually pretty simple, too.
So, we just need to keep asking follow-up questions.
Alright, since we're going to ask for more,
So, we need to bring the left sidebar back.
This is actually pretty simple.
Let's click this button one more time.
And the left sidebar is back.
And now we can just type in the input box.
and type in our question.
Let's get rid of the two notes in the top-left corner.
Yeah, that's definitely doable.
But for now, I want to show you guys another way to do it.
One that's more precise.
An even more convenient method.
We can click on this icon.
It's called 'annotate'.
Then, we can directly select the 'Two-parent Notes' section here.
Once selected, we can type in our suggestions for this area.
It's that simple.
Our instruction is simple: just remove those two words.
And then we submit the request. Alright.
As you can see, the request has been successfully submitted.
As you can see, it sent over two pieces of content in total.
One of them is a screenshot of the interface.
And the other one is our specific request.
So, once it gets the request,
Codex gets to work.
It should then remove this section.
Let's give it a moment.
Alright, Codex is done.
Let's open the preview area again.
Let's see how it turned out.
As you can see, that area from before is now completely gone.
Codex has already fixed the problem for us.
So, it looks like this annotate function is actually pretty handy.
Alright, let's just poke around this note-taking app a bit.
Let's see if there are any other issues we need to fix.
Looks like there's definitely a bug here.
When I click the plus button,
The idea is that it should add a new note.
But when I actually click it, nothing happens.
Looks like a bug.
So, let's tell Codex about this problem.
We need to tell Codex
After clicking the add button,
The note list area isn't responding at all.
Please investigate the cause.
I'll make the changes once I've confirmed it.
Alright, Codex has finished troubleshooting.
just as we asked.
Instead of jumping straight into changing the code,
Instead, it first provided a diagnostic result.
It suspects that the issue is most likely...
It's because of the local storage on the current page.
In other words, local storage has been disabled.
Yep, that's exactly it.
In other words, it's the preview pane on the right side of Codex.
There are some security restrictions.
This prevents certain features from working properly.
But if we switch over to a separate browser window,
And just like that, the problem is gone.
Don't believe me? Let's give it a try.
See? Now, if we click the 'add' button again...
See? It's working perfectly now.
Since the user is using our software in a real browser,
and not within Codex's preview area.
So, that's not even an issue to begin with.
So naturally, there's nothing to fix.
I'm not sure if this is a bug in Codex, or a feature.
But I'm pretty sure OpenAI designed it as a feature.
But in practice, it really does feel a bit like a bug.
So, if you're also building an external application,
So you'll definitely want to pay close attention to this.
Don't be fooled by the preview pane.
Now that we know the reason,
So, to avoid these limitations,
So, for the rest of this, we'll be working in a separate browser window.
to run the tests.
So, at this point, this most basic note-taking app...
So, even if we get it to run successfully,
Now, I want to circle back and talk about a detail we just ran into.
This is a request that Codex made.
Now, some of you might be wondering,
What if I give Codex a task and then go off to do something else?
and didn't realize it was waiting for my authorization.
That way, Codex won't just be stuck there waiting forever.
and when I get back, I find it hasn't done anything.
Just a huge waste of time.
So, is there a way to let it make decisions on its own?
Stop asking me for everything.
After all, no one wants to babysit it while it's working.
That would be way too exhausting.
Exactly, having to watch it all the time is a real pain.
Well, actually, Codex has already thought of that for us. The solution is right below the input box.
Alright, as you can see, there are three permission options here in total.
The first one is what we've just been using, the 'default permissions'.
In this mode,
If Codex needs to modify files outside of the project directory,
or needs to execute commands that could pose a security risk,
it will dutifully pop up a reminder.
Only after you give it the green light,
that it will continue with the task.
The upside of this mode is that it's absolutely safe.
Everything is under your control.
But the drawbacks are also very obvious.
Basically, it's completely dependent on you.
You have to be there to give it permission at all times.
The second one is Auto-Review.
In other words, auto-review.
This mode is pretty smart.
It introduces an agent dedicated to security reviews.
So, when Codex is about to perform an action,
This agent will first act as your gatekeeper.
If it's safe, it gets the green light.
and dangerous ones are blocked outright.
Only in very rare cases, when it's genuinely uncertain,
that it will pop up a window and ask you to make the call.
The third option is 'Full Access'.
As the name suggests,
This is basically the 'go wild' mode.
It automatically approves everything, letting Codex do whatever it wants.
You don't have to lift a finger.
This mode is definitely the most hands-off, that's for sure.
But that comes with its own risks.
What if it accidentally deletes some important data?
and you won't be able to stop it.
Now, the GPT-4o model is generally very reliable,
It generally won't do anything reckless.
But, as a responsible content creator,
But I still have to give you all a heads-up.
This mode has no safety checks whatsoever.
So think twice before you turn it on.
So, all things considered,
So, among these three modes,
Auto-review strikes the best balance between efficiency and security.
To avoid getting these pop-ups constantly later on,
It's asking us to click 'Agree'.
For the following demonstration,
So let's just switch everything over to auto-review mode.
Since we're on the topic of permission settings here,
Since we're on the topic, let's take a quick look.
So, what other settings are there next to the input box?
First, take a look at what's shown here: 5.5 and medium.
This means we're currently using the GPT-5.5 model.
The thinking depth is set to medium.
or medium, in other words.
If we click on it, we can see the thinking depth.
and it's fully adjustable.
It's divided into four levels: low, medium, high, and extra high.
The higher the depth of thought,
the longer Codex will take to process.
and the more tokens it will consume.
But generally speaking, the code it generates will also be of higher quality.
Besides adjusting the depth of thought,
We can also switch models right here.
In the dropdown list, besides GPT 5.5,
as well as GPT 5.4 and a whole series of other models.
So, you can pick one based on the specific difficulty of the task at hand.
And finally, you can also adjust the model's output speed right here.
Right now, it's set to 'standard'.
So, that's the standard speed.
And right next to it, there's a 'fast' option.
Once you enable the fast mode,
The generation speed will increase to 1.5 times the original.
But the trade-off is that your token consumption will also go up accordingly.
The exact amount of this increase depends on the model you're using.
For instance, with the 6PT5.5 model,
If you enable fast mode,
the token consumption will be exactly double that of the standard mode.
So, if money is no object for you,
and you've got plenty of tokens,
Then you can definitely turn on the fast mode.
This way, Codex will work much faster.
Alright, that's all we're going to cover for the input box configuration for now.
Alright, so our first version of the note-taking app is now up and running.
We've got the most basic functions up and running.
But to prevent things from getting messy when we add new features later,
So, it's a good idea to use Git to save our current version first.
This way, even if something goes wrong down the line,
we can also roll back to a working version at any time.
Just to be on the safe side.
In Codex, pulling up the terminal is super convenient.
We don't have to click through any menus.
Just hit the shortcut key, Command+J+I.
And as you can see, the terminal panel on the right just pops right up.
In here, we're going to enter a few standard Git commands one by one.
First, we'll run 'git init' to initialize the current project directory as a Git repository.
to initialize the current project directory as a Git repository.
Next, we're going to run git add.
This adds all the relevant files to the staging area.
And finally, we'll run git commit.
to commit our first set of changes. Alright.
Alright, once that's done,
And just like that, our code is safely backed up.
Now we can proceed with confidence.
to continue iterating on our product.
Once you're done with the terminal,
so it's not in the way.
All we have to do is press the same shortcut key again.
and Command+J will close it right up.
See? You can use a hotkey to open and close the terminal.
You never have to take your hands off the keyboard.
The whole process is incredibly smooth.
Which is also super convenient.
So, we've just built something with Codex.
a basic, functional note-taking app.
And we even committed a working version to Git.
So, let's continue to iterate on this note-taking app.
Let's make it more powerful and better-looking.
So, let's say you take a look at the note-taking app at this point.
and you feel that the color scheme isn't quite right.
There are a lot of green elements in here.
and you're not a big fan of green.
How about we try blue?
So, what should you do in this situation?
It's pretty simple.
You can just ask follow-up questions right here.
For instance, we could make a request like this.
But let's not send this request just yet.
Ah, but why is that?
Take a closer look.
In our last message, we had Codex troubleshoot the issue.
But to be honest,
But that's not really an issue.
It's just that the preview area in Codex has some limitations.
This troubleshooting process not only takes up the model's context window,
And it might even affect Codex's future executions.
It might just keep trying to fix the issue.
ending up breaking a page that was perfectly fine to begin with.
Although, to be fair, the chances of that happening are probably pretty low.
But if it's something we can avoid, we should definitely try to.
After all, this message is pretty much useless anyway.
So, what should we do?
There is a way.
And that is to just edit the last message.
See, there's an edit button right here.
We can just click on it, and that lets us edit the message directly.
Alright, let's give it a try.
Submit.
See? The original requirement has been replaced with our new one.
And just like that,
And just like that, the original message about troubleshooting the issue is gone.
Now that it's gone,
it will no longer take up the model's context window.
nor will it have any effect on Codex's subsequent operations.
So, as you can see, this feature is actually pretty useful in a lot of situations.
However, it's worth noting that
Codex only allows you to edit the very last message.
As for the messages that are even further back,
it doesn't actually let us edit them.
So, for all the messages further up the list, you won't see an edit button.
So, what if you want to edit an even earlier message?
One workaround is to use the 'fork' function, which we'll cover later on.
For now, you don't need to worry too much about it.
Alright, Codex has finished the task.
Let's see how it turned out.
Not bad.
Alright, let's go ahead and add the changes from this part to Git as well.
Before, we were using the command line to work with Git.
This method is precise and universally applicable.
But actually, Codex also has some built-in Git functions that we can use.
For example, we can start by clicking on this icon.
And in here, you'll find an area called 'Environment'.
This is all closely tied to how you use Git.
We can click on the 'changes' button right here.
And then, in this dropdown, you'll want to select the 'unstaged' option.
What you're seeing here are all the changes that haven't been committed yet.
the code that's in the staging area.
So, this is basically what Codex just changed.
If you think there's a problem with a specific line,
You can click the plus sign next to it.
Enter your request.
Once you've entered your request,
You can click the 'comment' button right here.
and have Codex make the corresponding changes.
But for now, we're not going to make any changes here.
Codex has done a great job with the task.
So, let's uncomment this line.
And using 'git commit' will submit these changes.
So, how do we do that?
It's pretty simple.
Just click the commit button right here.
Just type in the commit message, and you're good to go.
So our commit message will be: 'Change the overall theme to blue.'
And then click 'continue'.
And now, Codex will commit all the pending changes.
Alright, it's done.
Let's verify it.
First, press Command and the tilde key to open the terminal.
And then, run git log.
to check the Git commit history.
And you can see our commit has indeed gone through.
Once that's confirmed,
Let's press 'q' to exit the git log.
Then press Command and H to hide the terminal.
And with that, this feature is officially done.
Let's say at this point,
And you feel like the blue theme isn't that great either.
The more I look at it, the more I hate it.
How about we try a different one?
Sure thing.
Let's just submit the request directly.
Change the overall color scheme to purple.
After that's done, let's do another git commit.
Right, this time we're not going to handle git ourselves.
Manually using Git is a bit of a hassle.
Let's just have Codex handle it directly.
Before we commit,
And Codex gets to work.
Alright, let's give it a moment.
Alright, it's done.
Let's see the final result. Not bad.
And it did change to purple.
But, how should I put it... you still don't quite like it, do you?
But then you think, 'Ah, forget it.'
You know what? Maybe I'll just change it back to the original green.
Of course, that's possible.
As usual, you can just type it directly into the input box.
what you're asking for.
Just change it back to the original green.
This should definitely work.
The only problem is, this would make the model run all over again.
It's a bit of a waste of tokens.
So, we're not going to use this method.
Actually, our original state was the green one.
So, let's use Git to roll the code back to the green commit.
That version will do just fine.
However, this approach does have its drawbacks.
So, the code has been rolled back, that's for sure.
But the session's context is still stuck on the previous color scheme.
So, what if we want to repeat that within the current session?
Codex might think that the current color scheme is purple.
This could negatively impact the performance of any subsequent tasks.
So, can we roll back both the session and the code at the same time?
We just want to roll back to the version before we changed it to blue.
So, this version, right here. If there's a rollback function,
So it should be right next to this message.
There are some corresponding icons.
Let's see if we can find it.
Oh, there really is an icon. It looks kinda like it.
But it's not called 'rollback'.
It's called 'fork'.
So, 'fork' means that it's based on the current session.
and create a new copy from that point.
This new session will only include messages up to the one you've currently selected.
None of the subsequent messages will be included.
This is exactly what we're looking for.
So, what we want is for the session to stop right at the current message.
Since the session has changed,
So, will the code also automatically roll back?
Maybe it'll work, who knows.
Let's give it a shot.
First, let's click on this fork icon.
And two options pop up for us to choose from.
The first one is 'fork into local'.
and the other is 'fork into new workspace'.
The main difference between these two options is where the code for the new session will be stored.
The first option will continue using the current directory
as the storage location for the new session's code.
while the second option will create a new directory.
to store the code for the new session.
You might be feeling a bit lost right now,
But don't worry.
Let me show you, and it'll all make sense.
Before we get into the demo,
First, let's open up the sidebar.
This way, you'll get a better view.
Alright, the sidebar is open now.
Let's go ahead and click on this fork icon again.
And then, select the first option.
fork into local
As you can see, Codex has indeed created a new session for us.
And it's clearly marked right here.
This session is basically a copy of the other one.
Now, let's see if the code has been rolled back as well.
This is pretty straightforward.
We don't have to write any code.
We can just look at the final result.
Now, let's see if the page's color has changed.
As you can see, the page is still purple.
So, the code was never rolled back at all.
Exactly.
So, that's the thing about the 'fork into local' option.
It only processes the session's content.
It won't make any changes to the actual code at all.
But thankfully, we're using Git.
We can use Git to roll back the code.
First, let's open the terminal by pressing Command + J.
Then, we'll run the command 'git log'.
Let's figure out which commit we want to roll the code back to.
This should be the one.
Next, let's copy the hash value for this commit.
Finally, let's run this command.
And just like that, the code is rolled back to the version from that session.
Alright, let's head back to the browser and refresh the page.
Exactly.
Yep, it's definitely the green version from the very beginning.
Of course, the green isn't super obvious.
Only a few of the modules are green.
I'm having a bit of trouble describing this color scheme.
But in any case, the rollback was definitely successful.
I'm sure you can all see that.
So this is the 'fork into local' option.
So, by working with Git, we can get both the session and the code...
so that we can roll back both the session and the code to a previous state.
Alright, so there was another option just now, called 'fork into new worktree'.
So, what's that option for?
So, let's give it a try.
Alright, let's go back to the previous session.
Click on this fork icon.
And then select 'fork into new worktree'.
Notice how Codex has created a new session for us.
And it's a lot like 'fork into local'.
And this new session has been marked as well.
It's simply copied over from another session.
Everything seems pretty much the same as that 'fork into local' command.
So, what exactly has changed?
The answer lies in our current session.
The project directory it's pointing to has changed.
If you don't believe me, let's open up the terminal.
Let's type in 'pwd'. This command is used to display the current location.
So, as you can see, this is our current location.
the session I forked at the very beginning.
So, we're not actually operating in this directory.
If you don't believe me,
Let's go back to the session we forked at the very beginning.
Similarly, let's open the terminal and run 'pwd'.
As you can see, the project directories for these two are different.
I'll put both of these addresses up on the screen.
This way, you can see it more clearly.
So, this is one of the features of 'fork into new worktree'.
It will create a new session for the forked branch,
and create a corresponding new directory for it.
This means the new and old sessions are working on different codebases.
So they don't interfere with each other.
This is perfect for working in two separate sessions.
to work on two different features separately.
And once you're done, you can just merge them all together.
So, why is it called a 'worktree'?
That's because it's implemented using git worktree.
This is a feature of Git.
Now, if I were to explain this in detail...
that would take another few minutes to explain.
But this video is all about Codex,
not to get sidetracked on other things.
So, we'll just skip over git worktree for now.
If you're interested, you can look that up on your own.
Another thing worth mentioning is
fork into new worktree.
And it won't roll back your code either.
It simply takes all the code from the current project directory,
and copies them into a new directory.
And that's it.
Alright, so those are the two ways to fork a session.
So, to recap.
Both of these options will copy the session up to the selected message.
And neither of them will roll back your code for you.
The only difference between them is simply the location of the code.
The 'local' option continues to use the original directory.
while 'new worktree' creates a completely new, isolated directory.
So, that's the main difference.
So, regardless of which forking method you use,
neither of which will change the original code.
In fact, Codex also shows this right on the interface.
We can go back to the initial session.
And then, just click on the fork icon right here.
Did you catch that part?
So basically, what it's saying is that 'fork' is only for the conversation.
and it won't roll back the code.
Yeah, that's a bit of a roundabout way of saying it.
But yeah, that's basically what it means.
Alright, we've finally covered the fork function.
For now, we just need the first one, the 'fork into local' session.
The other one is 'fork into worktree'.
We don't need that for now.
So, can we just delete this session?
But to be precise,
So, when it comes to this session, there's a bit of a difference between archiving and deleting.
So, you can think of archiving as just temporarily hiding it.
Deleting, on the other hand, means it's gone for good.
Alright, let's give it a try.
Let's just click the icon next to the session.
And then click 'confirm'.
And the session gets archived.
See? The session is gone.
But unlike deleting it,
we can still get this session back.
First, let's press Command and comma.
and open the settings panel.
Then, click on 'Archive chats' inside.
And right here, we can see all the archived chats.
We can unarchive the conversation.
Or, you can permanently delete the session.
So, as you can see, there's a bit of a difference between deleting and archiving.
So that's all for the archiving feature.
So, from what we've done so far,
So, as we can see, this step is actually pretty important.
So, since it's so important,
So, can we get Codex to do something every time it finishes writing code?
to automatically make a Git commit?
That way, we don't have to go through the hassle of doing it manually every single time.
Of course, that's possible.
So, one way to do this is to just type it directly into the input box.
to tell Codex that after it's done with any code changes,
to make a git commit.
And then, just submit the request.
This way, in any subsequent operations,
Codex will definitely do exactly as we've instructed.
So, every time you finish writing some code, it's followed by a Git commit.
However, there's a major drawback to this method.
And that is, it only takes effect within the current session.
So, if we start a new session,
then Codex will completely forget about it.
So, what we need is a solution that works across sessions.
Even in a new session,
Codex can also help us with Git commits.
So, is that even possible?
Of course, it can.
And this is the agents.md file.
And this is where that file comes into play.
So, to put it simply, agents.md...
It's basically a configuration file that you place in the root directory of your project.
So, whenever Codex starts a new session,
it will automatically read this file.
and it will execute the contents as if they were its own instructions.
So, all we need to do is write our Git commit requirements into this file.
No matter how many new sessions we start,
Codex will remember that.
First, let's delete the original request.
We don't need this anymore.
Then, we'll click here to open this project directory in VSCode.
Let's create a new file in the root directory.
Let's name it agents.md.
And then, we'll write inside this file.
Every time you finish making changes to the code,
you need to make a git commit.
And just like that, the agents.md file has been created.
Let's go ahead and close VSCode.
Now, let's put it to the test.
and see if agents.md will actually take effect.
First, let's create a new session.
Then, we'll submit the request.
Add a theme toggle option in the bottom-left corner.
This will allow users to switch between light mode and dark mode.
Press Enter to submit.
Let's get Codex to work.
Alright, Codex is done.
Let's see how it turned out.
And sure enough, you can see a theme toggle button has appeared in the bottom-left corner.
Let's click on the corresponding theme.
and switch between the light and dark modes.
Looks absolutely perfect.
So, what we're most concerned about right now is...
So, did Codex actually perform the Git commit for us?
Alright, let's press Command+J to open the terminal, and run 'git log' to check it out.
And look, there's indeed a new commit right here.
And the message was written by Codex itself.
This proves that the agents.md file is actually working.
Even in a completely new session,
And Codex followed our instructions.
After the code modifications are complete,
and automatically made a Git commit.
So that's the basic usage of the agents.md file.
But of course, it can do so much more than just that.
For instance, you can specify the code style within it,
naming conventions,
technical stack requirements,
or even an introduction to your project's background, and so on.
So, every time Codex starts a new session,
it will read all these files.
This way, it will have a much better understanding of your project.
and the results it provides will be more accurate.
So, you could say, the better your agents.md file is written,
the smoother Codex will work for you.
But there's something you need to keep in mind.
Codex will only commit the code changes that are specific to the current task.
the agents.md file we created at the very beginning,
isn't part of the current requirement.
So, that's why Codex didn't commit it just now.
Let's click on 'changes' here.
Then, select 'unstaged'.
And you'll see that the content of agents.md hasn't been committed yet.
No worries, let's get this committed.
First, let's go ahead and click this commit button.
Then, just type in the commit message right in here.
Then, click 'continue'.
And just like that, the changes will be committed to Git.
Alright, everything went smoothly.
Let's start a new session.
Let's keep iterating on the note-taking app.
Right now, this software is essentially just an HTML file.
and can only be opened in a browser.
That's not very convenient.
So, we want to turn it into a proper desktop client.
This way, users can just double-click the icon to open it.
just like opening Codex in VS Code.
So, for the desktop client...
And Electron is a very popular choice for that.
And while we're at it, we can also bring in React and TypeScript.
Let's clean up the project structure.
This will make it easier to iterate on later.
So, let's just send our requirements directly to Codex.
Convert the web app into a desktop client.
For the tech stack, we'll use Electron, plus React.
And let's throw in TypeScript as well.
And be sure to run some tests.
and make sure all the core functions are working properly.
But keep in mind, this is a pretty big project.
So, it's best to have Codex create a rule for us first.
Once we've confirmed the rules are correct, we'll let it run.
To do that,
We can click the plus sign right here.
and then select 'plan mode'.
And just like that, Codex is in plan mode.
And you can see that from the icon, too.
In this mode,
Codex will first create a plan, and then write the code.
Alright, let's give it a shot.
As you can see, Codex has started working.
Alright, let's give it a moment.
Alright, it's going to ask us a few questions now.
Let's go ahead and make our selection.
First, where should the data be stored?
Let's just put it in a file.
And then, we just need it delivered to a point where it's ready for development and execution.
After that, Codex will get back to work.
As you can see, Codex is now starting to write the plan for us.
Let's just wait a little longer.
It's still in the process of stress testing.
Alright, it's done.
Let's take a look at the plan itself. It's actually quite comprehensive.
including various testing scenarios.
The architectural design is also laid out in great detail.
Then, Codex asks us,
So, should we go ahead and implement the code according to this plan?
So, it's giving us two options in total.
The first option is to just go ahead and agree.
and just start implementing the plan.
The second option is for if you're not satisfied with this plan.
you can just state your requirements.
In the text box, you can tell Codex what changes to make.
And then Codex will make the changes based on your feedback.
and generate a new plan.
So, we're not going to make any further changes to the plan here.
So let's just go ahead and approve it.
Alright, let's have Codex write the code for us based on this plan.
Alright.
Alright, Codex is getting to work now.
We'll need to wait for a little bit.
So, while we're waiting,
We can just chat with Codex about whatever we want.
We can type '-side' into the input box to open the side chat.
And in here, we can just ask Codex anything, bring up other topics.
These questions won't affect the task Codex is running on the left.
For instance, we could ask it something.
So, what other basic features do you think this note-taking app needs?
Submit.
Alright, Codex has given us a few viable options.
So, as you can see, while we're in the side chat,
The task execution on the left side in Codex wasn't interrupted at all.
And that right there is a really important feature of Side Chat.
Basically, it lets users, while Codex is in the middle of a task,
to ask some more lightweight questions.
And while Codex is answering these lighter questions,
without interrupting the main task on the left.
So, that's the main feature of the Side Chat function.
Alright, that's all we have for this part for now.
This architectural overhaul is quite a bit of work.
Codex still isn't finished.
Let's just be patient and wait a little longer.
Alright, looks like Codex has finished the task.
It's prompting us to use the command 'npm run dev'.
and that will start up the Electron app.
Alright, let's give it a shot.
First, press Command and the spacebar to open up a terminal.
Then, type in the command 'npm run dev' and hit Enter.
And just like that, the Electron app is up and running.
But it looks like there might be a problem.
It's basically just a blank screen.
Let's open up the console and see if there are any error messages.
Yep, there are definitely some errors.
Alright, we'll need Codex to help us fix this.
Alright, let's get back to Codex.
First, let's shut down this process.
And then, let's close the terminal.
And now, let's tell it what we want.
After launching, the console shows an error on a blank white screen.
It seems your previous testing wasn't thorough enough.
Please fix it.
And make sure to test it thoroughly after the fix before handing it back to me.
Codex agrees with me.
Let's wait for Codex to fix this error, and then we'll try again.
Looks like Codex has fixed it.
So, let's see how it works after the fix.
Alright, let's open up the terminal again.
And then, we'll run this command.
Alright, looks like it's working fine this time.
Adding notes works too.
We can also just type in any title we want here.
The content works fine, and switching themes is no problem either.
Looks pretty much perfect.
All the features are working as expected.
Alright, let's get back to Codex.
First, let's press Control+C to kill this process.
And then, let's collapse the terminal.
and switched it to an Electron framework.
Alright, let's go ahead and add a new feature.
So, our new requirement is to add Markdown support to this note-taking app.
Specifically, we need it in the top-right corner of the editor.
to add two buttons for switching between modes.
So, what if I want to start a new line right now?
Just hitting Enter won't work, of course.
Pressing Enter just submits it.
The right way to do it is to press Shift plus Enter.
See? That's how you hit Enter.
Let's continue by entering the task details.
First, we have the edit mode.
Displays all the text content.
and it will highlight the Markdown syntax within it.
And then, there's also the preview mode.
This is where you see the rendered output of the Markdown.
Now, hit Enter again.
Alright, you can see Codex has started working.
While it's working,
Let's create a new session.
Let's have it work on another, unrelated task.
So, our new task is to generate a logo for our notes project.
in SVG format.
As you can see, both sessions are now running.
Let's say, at this point, you suddenly have an idea.
Our note-taking app has both a light and a dark mode.
The logo needs to be clearly visible in both modes.
We'd better give Codex a little reminder.
Just so it doesn't forget, let's send the request.
But it looks like the request didn't go through.
It seems to be stuck here.
Exactly.
By default,
Only after the previous request is completed,
will Codex move on to the next request.
But by then, it's a bit too late.
After all, the logo has already been generated.
So, can we send this information to Codex right now?
How can we make it aware of this before it generates the logo?
Sure thing.
See this 'steer' button right here?
With a single click, our request will be sent to Codex immediately.
And just like that, we've achieved our goal.
Codex is still running.
Let's give it a moment.
Alright, as you can see, the logo has been generated.
Let's switch back to our original session.
Let's see how it's doing.
Looks like it's still running.
So, it looks like we'll have to wait a little bit longer.
Alright, both tasks are done.
Alright, let's just open up the app and see how it turned out.
First, we need to open the terminal.
And then, we'll run npm start.
Opening the Electron app.
Looks like there's a bit of an issue here.
The logo didn't load successfully.
So, we need to let Codex know about this.
Alright, first, let's shut down this Electron app.
First, let's see if the logo file is actually there.
So the logo is definitely in the public folder.
So, it's probably not a 'file not found' error.
Could it be an issue with the SVG file's format?
Let's head over to Finder and check it out.
Let's open the public folder.
So it looks like there's nothing wrong with the SVG file's format either.
After all, Finder is rendering it just fine.
Most likely, it's an issue with how Electron is loading the SVG file.
The method for loading this SVG file is the problem.
Alright, let's have Codex fix it.
First, press Command + J.
Let's bring up the session list.
Then, select the session for generating the logo.
And then, in here, we'll type in our specific question.
The logo isn't showing up.
After we submit it,
And Codex starts troubleshooting the issue for us.
Let's just wait a little longer.
And the fix is complete.
Alright, let's launch the app again and see how it turned out.
First, open up the terminal and run 'npm start'.
Alright, looks like the logo is showing up successfully this time.
We can also just click around and check out some of the other features.
Let's see if everything's running smoothly.
For Markdown, let's just type in a few keywords.
Let's see if the syntax highlighting is working properly.
It seems like everything is working as expected.
All the different formats are displayed perfectly.
So, as you can see, the preview looks good too.
And that's all for this requirement.
Alright, let's get back to Codex.
Let's keep iterating on it.
So far, we've only covered the basic capabilities of Codex.
Next up, let's talk about plugins.
You can think of a plugin as an add-on for Codex.
This gives Codex the corresponding capabilities.
and help Codex do more things.
I know that might sound a bit abstract.
Let's see it in action.
First, let's open up the sidebar.
and then click on 'plugins' inside.
And right here, we can see all the available plugins.
Some of them can control your computer,
ones for controlling Chrome,
There are also ones for editing Excel.
There are also some for creating PowerPoint presentations.
If there's a checkmark next to the plugin,
That means the plugin is already installed.
If a plugin isn't installed,
you'll see a plus sign next to it.
We can just click the plus sign to install it.
Let's just click on a plugin at random.
Let's see what's inside.
For example, we can click on this plugin called Gmail.
As you can see, the plugin is made up of three components.
One of them is an app,
And the other two are skills.
This app is what connects Codex and Gmail.
It comes with a lot of tools.
Of course, Codex doesn't actually call them 'tools'.
Codex calls them 'actions'.
But in essence, these are just individual tools.
It's pretty much like the tools in MCP.
Let's compare it with 'apply labels to emails'.
So, this one is for labeling emails.
Archive emails, which is used for archiving emails.
In total, this app provides 24 tools just like these.
Besides the app,
This plugin also provides two skills.
So basically, you can think of a Skill
as an instruction manual for the large model.
Take the Gmail skill, for instance.
It spells out exactly how to summarize the content of an email,
how to draft a reply,
and which tools to use in which situations, and so on.
And this skill, called 'inbox triage',
is to tell the large model how to categorize emails.
For instance, which emails are urgent,
which ones need a reply, and so on.
If you're interested in learning more about skills,
you can check out my video.
I'll explain everything about how to use skills and how they work in one go.
So, the Gmail app itself only consists of these three components.
So, if we choose to install the Gmail plugin,
So, basically, you're just installing these three components.
So, when the user wants Codex to do something with Gmail,
the GPT model will then find these three components
and then use their capabilities and instructions to fulfill the user's request.
So, that's basically how it works.
Let's look at a specific example.
For example, let's say we have 'presentations'.
This plugin is for creating PowerPoint presentations.
It only has one component.
And that would be this skill, called 'presentations'.
This skill gives you a detailed breakdown of what to do.
to create a high-quality presentation.
So now, let's try using this plugin called 'presentations'.
to get what we need done.
Alright, let's start a new session.
And now, let's type in our request.
Create a PowerPoint presentation for this note-taking app.
to introduce its product design and technical architecture.
Once you submit it,
Codex will then find what we mentioned earlier.
the plugin called 'presentations'
and use the capabilities provided by that plugin to create the PowerPoint.
Of course, if you're worried that Codex might not find this plugin,
Or, if I got it wrong,
You can explicitly tell Codex
to use this plugin called 'presentations'.
All you have to do is type an @ symbol at the very beginning of your task.
Then, type in 'presentations' and hit Enter.
This way, Codex will definitely use the 'presentations' plugin.
Time to make a PPT.
But it's fine if you don't add it, though.
Codex will find the plugin automatically anyway.
So, we'll just get rid of it for now.
Alright, let's commit.
As you can see, Codex has started working.
Let's give it a moment.
Codex is done.
Let's open it up and see.
Nothing too fancy, but it gets the job done.
But there's actually still a lot of room for improvement here.
But it's a decent starting point nonetheless.
So, we can build upon this and make some further improvements.
This plugin, called Presentations, isn't particularly impressive.
Alright, let me introduce you to OpenAI.
two very practical plugins that it provides.
One is called Computer Use,
for controlling your computer.
and the other is called Chrome.
to control the Chrome browser.
Let's start by trying out the Chrome plugin.
Let's head over to the plugin management section.
Then, click the plus sign next to Chrome to install the plugin.
Click 'Install for Chrome'.
Alright, it's installed.
Then, Codex prompts us,
So, we also need to install the corresponding extension on Chrome. Alright.
So, let's just follow its instructions to install the extension.
Alright, with everything set up,
So, let's give the Chrome extension a try.
We can just click the button right next to it.
And just like that,
Codex will then initialize one for us.
Let's use the request it's provided for us.
We can just get rid of the rest of it.
So, for our specific requirements,
So, the first step is to open the Product Hunt homepage.
Then, find the three most popular, newly launched products from today.
and summarize the key features of each.
and include the links to them.
Alright, let's hand it over.
So you can see it more clearly,
Let me just shrink Codex down a bit.
and bring up the Chrome browser.
This way,
so you can all see it more clearly.
So, how exactly does Codex get the job done?
As you can see, Codex has created a tab group.
This tab group is specifically for solving our problem.
Then, within this tab group, it navigated to the Product Hunt homepage.
And here we have the three hottest newly launched products of the day.
And I'm sure Codex has seen it too.
And as you can see, Codex is now opening up another tab.
So this looks like the first product.
It's a website related to Brew.
And now it's opened another one.
Alright, we're just gonna let it do its thing now.
Codex will probably check out a few more web pages.
So let's just wait here for a moment.
I'm sure it'll be able to search all the product pages in a moment.
and then give us some pretty useful feedback.
Let's just wait for a moment.
Alright, Codex has summarized it for us.
And this is pretty much the result we were looking for.
So, that's how you use the Chrome extension.
Alright, let's maximize Codex again.
Alright, next up, let's take a look at how to use the Computer Use plugin.
how to use this plugin.
This one is for controlling your computer.
Similarly, we click on the plus sign.
Then, go ahead and install it.
Installation complete.
Let's give it a try.
It's similar to how you'd use Chrome.
We can also click the small icon next to 'Computer Use'.
And just like that, it will start a related Computer Use session.
First, let's delete this last part of the text.
Because it's not really relevant to the request we're actually making.
And then let's make a small change.
The directory corresponding to the request.
Right now, we're in the 'Mark Notes' folder.
But the request we actually want to make...
It doesn't really have much to do with this project.
So we're just going to choose "Don't work in the project."
So basically, this is just a random request we're making.
This way, it won't be tied to any specific project directory. And now, we can officially start entering our requests.
So, the request is: 'Please open the calendar app on my computer.'
Create a new event for May 28th at 10 AM.
The title will be 'Discussing the Future Design of Mark Notes'.
Yep, just like that.
Now, let's have Codex operate the calendar application.
And just like before,
Let's minimize Codex.
and reveal the calendar app.
This way, you can all see it more clearly.
So, how does Codex actually operate our calendar software?
Alright, so the first thing Codex does is ask us for permission to use the calendar application.
We'll grant it access.
And as you can see, Codex is now in action.
So this is Codex's mouse cursor.
It's a completely separate system from the mouse we're actually using.
They don't interfere with each other at all.
And then, Codex starts controlling the mouse.
to get the job done for us.
Now, it needs us to confirm.
So, it's asking if we're sure we want to create this schedule.
That's a bit wordy.
Of course, we're confirming.
Let's give it a reply.
Alright, it looks like Codex has done what we asked.
Alright, let's take a look.
Looks like the title and time slot for this schedule...
Everything is just as we requested.
Alright, then we're all set.
Alright, let's maximize Codex again.
So, this is basically the Computer Use feature.
So, that's how you use this plugin.
It's worth mentioning that
Codex uses its own separate virtual mouse, so it won't interfere with your actual mouse at all.
I just brought the calendar app to the front.
I'm just doing this for demonstration purposes.
In fact, you can just let it work quietly in the background.
and just carry on with whatever you were doing.
You can even browse the web or watch videos.
It won't slow you down at all. Alright, that's everything on Computer Use.
Alright, next up, let's see how to use Skills.
So, if you want to browse the skills,
we first have to open up the plugins.
And then, click on 'Skills' in here.
And you'll see a list of available skills.
Actually, when we were using plugins earlier,
we've actually already been using skills indirectly.
Because whether it's for presentations,
computer use, or even Chrome,
The core component for all these plugins is the Skill.
You can find all of them under the 'Skills' tab.
So, when we install the corresponding plugins,
the related skills will be installed along with it.
So, that's where we can find all these skills.
However, there is one ace-in-the-hole skill.
It's listed separately under the 'skill' tab.
And it doesn't have a corresponding plugin.
And that skill is imagegen.
And it's used for generating images.
I'm sure you've all heard about GPT's image generation capabilities by now.
Not only are they beautiful,
and it's also very affordable.
Now, let's use a skill to create an image.
Let's start a new session under the Mark Notes project.
Then, we'll input our request.
Generate a promotional poster image for the note-taking app.
Make sure to use the actual software screenshots I provided.
Next, we need to provide Codex with the corresponding software screenshots.
First, let's press Command + Space to open the terminal.
Then, run the command 'npm start' to launch our note-taking app.
Alright, let's head back to Codex and click the plus sign.
And then, find the option that says 'attach electron'.
So, the Electron here is basically...
our Mark Notes software.
Our note-taking app is built with Electron.
So, from Codex's perspective,
So, this notes app is called Electron.
Let's go ahead and click on this option.
Once we click on it,
Codex is asking us if we want to enable this feature.
We'll click 'enable'.
And just like that, the screenshot of our Mark Notes is right there in the chat box.
This way, when Codex is designing the poster,
it can work based on a real screenshot of the software.
Pretty convenient, right?
Just click the button, and it'll paste the screenshot right in.
But that's not even the most convenient part.
Codex also provides a hotkey for this.
Just one press and you can send over the screenshot.
Let me show you how it works.
The screenshot we gave Codex earlier was for the light mode.
Now, I'm sending Codex a screenshot in dark mode.
Alright, let's go back to Mark Notes and switch it to dark mode.
And here's the key part.
Press the left and right Command keys at the same time.
And just like that, we've got a screenshot of MarkNote in dark mode.
And I've sent that over to Codex as well.
This is definitely way more convenient.
Alright, so now Codex has screenshots for both light and dark modes.
Alright, let's have it start making the poster.
Submit.
First, we can see that
Codex will use ImageGen.
This is the skill we mentioned earlier, and we're going to use it to create this promotional poster.
Alright, let's just give it a moment.
Let's see what it comes up with.
Alright, it's done. I think it's pretty decent.
And it did base it on our screenshot.
So, what do you think?
Besides using the skills that Codex installs for us,
We can also create our own skills.
Let's press Command+J to start a new session.
And then, we'll input our task.
Write a code review skill.
to be used specifically for the current project.
This skill should include the following rules.
Alright, let's commit it.
As you can see, the skill is now ready.
We'll just call it 'marknotes-code-review'.
Alright, let's press Command + J, L, N to start a new session.
Let's see how this skill works.
First, let's add this skill.
And then, we can make our request.
Check the current project's code for any issues.
Alright, we're good to go.
Alright, the results are in. Now, we can also have Codex...
to modify the code based on the review results.
Alright, I won't go any further with this demonstration.
Our note-taking app is being iterated on daily.
The code gets updated daily.
So, it's a good idea to have a daily, scheduled check for our code.
to see if there are any issues.
This is exactly the kind of scenario that's perfect for setting up a scheduled task to handle.
And Codex offers this exact feature.
So, let's click on these three dots right here.
Then, click on 'add automation'.
So, we're adding a scheduled task.
This is where you enter the title for the automation task.
Codex has already filled this in for us.
So, here's what you fill in when you're setting up the scheduled task.
So, here's the request we need to send to Codex.
Our request is to check the code in the current project.
and report any issues.
And below that, we have the execution environment.
There are three options in total.
They are: local, worktree, and chats.
The 'local' option runs scheduled tasks within a specific project directory.
A 'worktree' is a new worktree created based on an existing project directory.
The scheduled task will then run inside this new worktree.
We've covered the concept of a worktree before.
It's a concept in Git.
If you're still a bit confused about this,
You can ignore that for now; we won't be using this option here.
Chats is the execution environment.
It's not tied to any specific project directory.
Remember when we used the Chrome plugin to search the web earlier?
We were actually using the Chats environment.
So, for our purposes, the 'local' option is the best fit here.
After all, for our scheduled task,
The goal is to scan the project code for the Mark Notes app.
So, it absolutely has to be tied to a specific project directory.
Let's select 'local'.
And then, in here, we're going to select Mark Notes.
And over here, we have the frequency.
We'll go with 'daily'.
As for the specific time, let's just keep it at 9 o'clock.
So basically, this is our scheduled task.
to start at 9 AM every day.
Next, let's select the model. We'll go with GPT-5.5 for the inference strength.
We'll just stick with the current 'medium' setting.
Then, we'll click 'save'.
Now, let's open the sidebar on the left again.
And there we can see 'Automations'.
And there's an extra '1' in here.
After clicking on it, you can see the scheduled task we just created.
It will start running at 9 AM every day.
Each time it runs, it will create a new session.
We can click this button to run a test of the scheduled task.
And you can see a new session has been created.
This is what's used to run scheduled tasks.
Let's open it up and take a look.
Alright, as you can see, the scheduled task is now complete.
And it will run just like this every day from now on.
And that's the scheduled task.
And finally, I want to talk about
Now, for a really practical feature of Codex.
And that is Codex mobile.
Basically, it means we can use our phones to control Codex and have it complete tasks for us.
Let's go ahead and tap on Codex mobile right here.
And then, click 'get started'.
And then, tap 'Allow'.
This will let your phone control this computer.
And then, click 'done'.
After you've clicked 'done',
Codex should then display a QR code for you.
If the QR code doesn't show up for you, like what happened to me,
You can click on the phone icon right here.
And just like that, the QR code appears.
Next, we'll need to open our phone's camera.
and scan this QR code.
And that will take us to the Codex page on ChatGPT.
And from here, we can start sending commands to the Codex on our computer.
For example, let's say we want it to do something with our calendar.
Do you remember what we did with the calendar earlier?
created an event.
Let's title it 'Discussing the Next Steps for Mark Notes Design'.
Now, let's send another command from our phone.
and have it remove this calendar event.
Let's click on the chat.
And then, we'll click here.
Look for the 'Computer Use' option in there.
Next, we need to type in our request.
Our request is to take the event on May 28th in the calendar...
delete the schedule for the Mark Notes discussion.
Once it's written, don't rush to submit it just yet.
Alright, as you can see, we're now in the MarkNote project directory.
But our request actually has nothing to do with this project's...
the code itself doesn't really have anything to do with it.
We just want to work with the calendar app.
So, we need to click on the settings button again.
Then, we'll choose to not use a project.
Alright, with that, everything's set.
We submit the request.
First, Codex asks for our permission to proceed.
this calendar software.
We'll grant it.
Then, Codex asks us again if we're sure we want to delete this event.
We'll confirm.
And then Codex starts taking control of the computer.
Let me show you what's happening on the computer.
See? There's a mouse cursor on the calendar now.
It's now controlling the computer to delete this calendar event.
Alright, it's deleted.
And just like that, we're controlling the computer with our phone.
Pretty convenient, right?
This way, you can use Codex even when you're on the go.
to get all sorts of things done.
Alright, and that's a wrap for this video.
This is Mark, breaking down the most hardcore tech in the simplest terms.
tech.
See you in the next one.
Bye-bye.